<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Art Space App</string>
    <string name="beauty_of_nature">Luminous Lake</string>
    <string name="beauty_of_nature_description">The image is a digital artwork of a tree in the middle of a lake. The tree is tall and has a lot of leaves, and it looks like it is floating on the water. The lake is blue and green, and it reflects the colors of the sky and the mountains. The mountains are in the background, and they are tall and snow-capped. The sky is blue and white, and it has a few clouds.</string>
    <string name="mountain_village">Mountain Village</string>
    <string name="mountain_village_description">The painting depicts a tranquil village nestled amidst rolling hills and lush greenery. A gentle river winds its way through the center of the village, its surface reflecting the vibrant hues of the sky. The warm glow of the setting sun bathes the scene in a golden light, casting long shadows from the quaint, thatched-roof cottages that line the riverbank. Smoke curls gently from chimneys, adding to the air of serenity.</string>
    <string name="harbour_twilight">Harbor Twilight</string>
    <string name="harbour_twilight_description">The painting depicts a bustling harbor scene in a quaint coastal village. The warm glow of the setting sun casts long shadows across the cobbled streets and bathes the colorful houses in a soft golden light. Fishing boats bob gently in the calm waters of the harbor, their nets laden with the day\'s catch. Seagulls wheel and cry overhead, their calls mingling with the lively chatter of villagers going about their evening routines.</string>
    <string name="sir_waggington">Sir Waggington</string>
    <string name="sir_waggington_description">The painting depicts a dapper dog dressed in a charcoal grey suit and a bright red tie, standing against a plain white background. The dog\'s breed is difficult to discern, but it has short, dark fur, floppy ears, and a slightly stocky build. Its paws are tucked neatly beneath its body, and its tail curves gently upwards in a relaxed posture. The tie is the most eye-catching element of the photo, standing out against the dog\'s grey fur and adding a touch of whimsy to its formal attire. The dog\'s expression is serious and contemplative, its head tilted slightly to the side as if it\'s posing for a portrait.</string>
</resources>